export const physicalQuestions = [
  {
    question:
      "I exercise aerobically (vigorous, continuous exercise) for 20 to 30 minutes at least three times per week.",
    ans: "question1",
  },
  {
    question: "I eat fresh fruits, vegetables, and whole grains every day.",
    ans: "question2",
  },
  { question: "I avoid tobacco products.", ans: "question3" },
  {
    question: "I wear a seat belt while riding in or driving a car.",
    ans: "question4",
  },
  {
    question: "I avoid drinking caffeinated and sugary beverages.",
    ans: "question5",
  },
  {
    question: "I get an adequate amount of sleep (7-9 hours/night).",
    ans: "question6",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I keep up with my annual physical, dental checkups, immunizations, and self-exams.",
    ans: "question7",
  },
  {
    question: "I maintain a reasonable weight for my age and height.",
    ans: "question8",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I brush my teeth at least twice daily, and floss at least once daily.",
    ans: "question9",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I use stress management techniques that help me to stay calm and relaxed.",
    ans: "question10",
  },
];

export const intellectualQuestions = [
  {
    question: "I make an effort to learn new things.",
    ans: "question1",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I try to keep on top of current affairs locally, nationally, and internationally.",
    ans: "question2",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I listen to lectures, plays, and musical performances inperson or online.",
    ans: "question3",
  },
  {
    question: "I do creative and stimulating mental activities/games.",
    ans: "question4",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I read daily, whether that be the newspaper, the internet, magazines, or books from my local bookstore or library.",
    ans: "question5",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I practice something every week to improve my skills and use my gifts, such as crafts, cooking, music, or sports.",
    ans: "question6",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I try to see more than one side of an issue, especially for things that are controversial.",
    ans: "question7",
  },
  {
    question: "I engage in intellectual discussions.",
    ans: "question8",
  },
  {
    question: "I look up things that I don' know.",
    ans: "question9",
  },
  {
    question: "I ask questions to learn from others.",
    ans: "question10",
  },
];

export const environmentalQuestions = [
  {
    question: "I regularly clean my living and work environment.",
    ans: "question1",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I make maximal use of natural light, fresh air, and live plants.",
    ans: "question2",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I discard garbage regularly, clean spoiled foods out of the refrigerator, and stay on top of any pet odors.",
    ans: "question3",
  },
  {
    question: "I tidy my home and work spaces in order to prevent clutter and stay organized.",
    ans: "question4",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I conserve energy (fuel, electricity, water, etc.) in my home, my car, and elsewhere.",
    ans: "question5",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I recycle (glass, paper, plastic, etc.).",
    ans: "question6",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I do not litter.",
    ans: "question7",
  },
  {
    question: "I purchase recycled items when possible.",
    ans: "question8",
  },
  {
    question: "I set aside time to enjoy nature.",
    ans: "question9",
  },
  {
    question: "I set aside time to reflect and/or practice mindfulness.",
    ans: "question10",
  },
];

export const spiritualQuestions = [
  {
    question: "I can name my own personal values and describe my beliefs about life.",
    ans: "question1",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I make conscious choices about my daily actions based on my personal values.",
    ans: "question2",
  },
  {
    question:
      "When I get depressed or frustrated, I draw on my beliefs and values to give me direction.",
    ans: "question3",
  },
  {
    question: "I use prayer, meditation, and/or quiet personal reflection regularly in my life.",
    ans: "question4",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Life is meaningful for me, and I feel a purpose in life.",
    ans: "question5",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I try to learn about others' beliefs and values, especially those that different from my own.",
    ans: "question6",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I have a strong sense of optimism and faith in the future.",
    ans: "question7",
  },
  {
    question: "I use my thoughts and attitudes in life-affirming ways.",
    ans: "question8",
  },
  {
    question: "I appreciate the natural forces that exist in the universe.",
    ans: "question9",
  },
  {
    question: "I feel gratitude for the good things in my life.",
    ans: "question10",
  },
];

export const socialQuestions = [
  {
    question: "I have a network of friends and/or family.",
    ans: "question1",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I contribute time and/or money to social and community projects or causes.",
    ans: "question2",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I regularly spend time with people I like.",
    ans: "question3",
  },
  {
    question: "I balance my own needs with the needs of others.",
    ans: "question4",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I am a compassionate person and try to help others when I can.",
    ans: "question5",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I have a sense of belonging within my community.",
    ans: "question6",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I feel comfortable meeting new people.",
    ans: "question7",
  },
  {
    question: "I can give and receive compliments graciously.",
    ans: "question8",
  },
  {
    question: "I communicate with and get along with a wide variety of people.",
    ans: "question9",
  },
  {
    question: "I am interested in others, including those with backgrounds that are different from my own",
    ans: "question10",
  },
];